Two birds with one stone.
You used the ghost rumors
to abolish Lin Wanmei's overtime policy.
It undermined her authority,
drove a wedge between her and Xiaoxiao,
and won over the R&D Department.
Isn't that two birds with one stone?
What are you going to do about it?
I'm not going to do anything.
But I know
your true motive
isn't just about Chu Yan, is it?
Tell me.
I might be able to help you.
This is my own business.
Stay out of it.
I am the company's CEO.
I have the right to know everything that happens here.
What if
it severely impacts the company?
Whatever the impact,
I'll handle it myself.
CEO An,
save that speech for the shareholders.
Don't waste it on me.
You really want to know?
Well, I'm not telling you.
You knew she was targeting Lin Wanmei,
yet you didn't stop her.
There must be more to Chu Yan's suicide.
Sang Luo isn't the only one who wants to know.
I want to know too.
So you plan to keep indulging Sang Luo?
Aren't you afraid she'll blow things out of proportion?
A vibrant life was lost.
Everyone who pushed her to her death
must pay the price.
You scared me.
What are you doing here?
I should be asking you that.
Since when do you have this hobby
of working out all by yourself?
I've just been so busy with work lately.
I need to exercise more
to maintain my muscles.
You're lying.
When have I ever lied to you?
We had a deal.
We'd take down Lin Wanmei together,
and then you'd promote me.
But Sang Luo is still here.
She's just a bitch.
It doesn't matter what she is.
She still holds the title
of Genius Winemaker.
I can't just casually
put you in the Director position.
I'm leading a company,
an entire group.
I have to convince everyone,
right?
Well, you're the leader.
You pretty much have the final say.
Come up with something for me.
Lately,
I have been thinking of a way for you.
Go apologize to Lin Wanmei.
Give her a way out.
I'm sick of her.
No way.
As for a solution,
I already gave you one.
You should
think it over yourself.
You got what you wanted and now you're ditching me?
Are you even a man?
Pfft!
Pfft, pfft, pfft!
If that's how you're going to be,
then I can't help you at all.
You're on your own.
Fine.
If that's the case,
I'll just have to give this
to someone else.
Like who?
Cheng An.
What is this?
Something good to take down Lin Wanmei.
Now you see its value.
Are you willing to help me now?
Baby,
if you'd told me you had this earlier,
wouldn't we have
taken down Lin Wanmei a long time ago?
Did you come back for me
or for this thing?
You ran off so fast just now.
You're the most important person to me.
How could I not help you?
That's more like it.
Listen to me,
this is the key evidence
that Lin Wanmei drove Chu Yan to her death.
Contact your media friends.
We need to blow this up as big as possible
to help me get even.
Leave the rest
to me.
An anonymous source recently revealed
a female executive at a major liquor group
allegedly forced an intern to drink,
leading to her suicide.
A leaked video also shows what seems to be
the intern crying for help under assault.
This has caused a massive public uproar.
Lin Wanmei, come out!
Lin Wanmei!
Step back.
You can't hide.
Yanyan.
Will Yanyan's humiliation
finally be washed away?
This is only the beginning.
The atrocities they committed against Chu Yan
will definitely be punished.
After a thorough investigation, the police
successfully arrested three suspects
for forcing Valley Breeze Group staff
to drink and sexually assaulting them.
Major twist in Valley Breeze Group scandal.
The real mastermind is someone else.
Cut the crap.
Five million.
Once I step out of Valley Breeze Group,
I won't say a word about your dirty deeds.
It's so late.
What do you want?
Cheng Yan.
Help me intercept a news story.
Someone is inciting a cybermob against me.
I know.
I bought those internet trolls just for you.
They're pretty good at steering the narrative, right?
It was you.
Why?
Why would you do this to me?
Cheng Yan!
Someone with no use to me...
why would I keep you around?
You...
Such a nice girl.
I really hate to see you go.
What a pity.
You used the Public Relations Department
to steer public opinion
and pin everything on Xiaoxiao.
Sister-in-law.
My show of sincerity...
It's not bad, right?
She
is just an insignificant nobody.
If you can handle Mom for me,
then that will prove
you have what it takes to work with me.
Oh, Sister-in-law...
you really are a bit too greedy.
If you can't even handle this,
then there's nothing more to say.
As long as you're willing to take my side
and help take Cheng An down,
handling Mom
is just a matter of a few words.
You know where I stand with Mom.
It's just that...
I'm afraid you might hold back.
After all, you and the third brother
had a history together.
Let me give you a piece of advice, Cheng Yan.
If you really want to work with me,
you'd better not cross the line.
You backstabbing, manipulative bitch!
Hope you get hit by a car!
When you look in the mirror,
doesn't your vicious face make you sick?
Go to hell! Die!
It's not my fault!
It's not!
Someone's trying to kill me!
Murder!
Open the door!
Do you have a phone?
Hello?
Is this the police?
What are you doing?
I want to turn myself in!
I need to turn myself in right now!
The people who assaulted Chu Yan
and Xiaoxiao are already in prison.
But Lin Wanmei still got away.
Actually, I should have known
she would never admit defeat so easily.
I've already had my people look into it.
It was Xiaoxiao who leaked the news to Cheng Yan.
But Cheng Yan switched sides at the last minute
and helped Lin Wanmei in the end.
It looks like they've joined forces.
I wonder who their gun
will be aimed at next.
Auntie.
I'm so sorry.
I failed Chu Yan.
I was such a coward.
I didn't step up to help her in time.
This is Chu Yan's diary,
and her favorite sunshine doll.
These are all my favorites.
Yanyan.
You need to listen to your boss at work.
That way, they will like you.
Director Lin.
My mom brewed this herself.
Longan and red ginseng paste.
It has no weird additives.
For cold hands and feet,
it works wonders.
Give it a try.
Thank your mom for me.
Everyone, have a taste.
These are cupcakes my mom made.
They're delicious. Thanks.
Smells so good.
Smells great. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Supervisor Xiao.
Who knows if they're even clean,
handing them out like this.
This... This...
Alright.
Let's go.
It's all my fault.
I thought kindness begets kindness,
but I ended up harming her instead.
Auntie.
I deserve to die.
It's all my fault.
Yanyan!
Chu Yan
was part of the R&D Department.
As the head of the R&D Department,
Lin Wanmei,
do you have anything to say?
Um,
I must say a few words for Director Lin.
Everyone knows
that Director Lin is pregnant.
She's been running around for this matter
to clarify the truth.
I think
she has done her duty.
Who told her to go?
She brought so much shame to the Cheng family.
How does she even have the nerve to go out
and show her face in public?
At the end of the day,
the Public Relations Department got the news
and decided to handle it passively.
If we had received the news earlier
and faced it actively,
things wouldn't have turned out like this.
Cheng An,
as the CEO of the company,
with such a huge mess happening,
you can't escape the blame.
So please, CEO An,
take the fall and resign
to give everyone an explanation.
I see what's going on here.
This meeting today
is just a trap set up against CEO An!
We are all civilized people.
Aren't we just solving the problem?
Solving the problem, huh?
Come here!
I'll solve the problem with you! What are you doing?
What are you doing? I think you
are the biggest problem!
Speak!
Am I right?
Stop hitting him!
Stop fighting!
Partying and drinking every single day!
I'll kill you! Stop hitting!
Stop hitting!
Speak! It's all his fault!
Get up!
I'll kill you!
Get up! Get up!
I'm going to kill him!
Pull him away, quick!
Let me go!
Tell me,
is it your fault?
Don't pull me!
A hot Americano.
At a time like this,
why aren't you anxious at all?
Cheng Yan is not cut out to run a company.
If we just leave him be,
Valley Breeze Group will soon be ruined.
You must have a backup plan, right?
Thank you.
What backup plan could I have?
I'll just treat it as a vacation.
Are you really giving up?
I'm not giving up.
I've been in the thick of it all these years,
so there are things I can't see clearly.
Taking a break now
allows me to stand as an outsider
and study Valley Breeze Group.
You can't go on like this.
You need to relax a bit.
Cheer up a bit.
Maybe you'll get some different ideas.
Let me do a happy dance for you.
Ears, ears, smile a bit.
Nose, nose, smile a bit.
Mouth, mouth, smile a bit.
I have to submit it tomorrow.
They're all smiling.
You need...
You really need to relax.
Maybe then you'll figure it out by tomorrow.
Sometimes you have to learn to slow down.
Take an outsider's perspective
and look at it again.
You might find something different.
Ye Xiaowei changed me a lot.
It's just too bad
that she is forever stuck in the past.
She stopped in the past.
But your life goes on.
It's time to move on.
I'll be at the winery for the time being.
Wait.
I think
you might need to see this.
From now on,
as long as you work hard for me,
if I'm making a fortune,
we will
make a fortune together.
Thank you for believing in me, Uncle.
I'll definitely stick with you and make a fortune.
Then from now on, we'll
rely on you, CEO Yan.
As long as you say that,
that's enough.
They say a new boss lights a new fire.
I just took over the company,
and this fire
must burn fiercely.
Zhuge Kongming,
Zhou Gongjin,
help me strategize.
How to boost Valley Breeze Group's profit?
Well, I
don't know much about running the company.
But the way I see it,
if we want to boost profits,
there are only two ways.
Either raise prices,
or lower costs.
Raising prices isn't an option.
According to my market research,
everyone's cutting back on spending now.
If you raise the prices,
the customers will just run away.
Then we can only start by lowering costs.
I can control costs on the R&D end.
Well,
R&D is the top priority of our company.
For years, Valley Breeze Group
has maintained a strong market foothold
by continuously launching new products.
I'm worried that
if R&D costs are lowered,
it will affect the company...
Luoluo,
your thinking is a bit too rigid.
Ordinary consumers don't know that much.
As long as it tastes good, that's enough.
Right.
Lin Wanmei,
haven't you
always been in touch with the lab in California?
Learn from them
to lower costs
and develop new products.
Okay.
CEO Yan.
My dear niece,
Uncle needs to give you a good talking-to.
You need to learn to be flexible.
The business world is a battlefield.
You have to adapt.
Otherwise,
your room for advancement will be very limited.
Yes,
Uncle is right.
I see that
Uncle is about to become
the chairman of Valley Breeze Group.
So I also prepared some documents
for you to look at.
Valley Breeze Group's net profit report.
The way I see it,
we should
optimize production line resources,
allocate them rationally,
and boost overall efficiency.
This ice wine,
the cost is so high,
but the profit is so low.
It runs counter
to our strategic layout.
Perfect timing.
Send a notice down.
Valley Breeze Group
will no longer produce ice wine.
Cut the entire production line.
CEO Yan,
we've already signed agreements with the fruit farmers.
They are about to start harvesting.
What agreements?
They're just a bunch of powerless, poor fruit farmers.
Just peasants.
It's settled then.
Yes.
Brilliant move, Uncle.
In the tasting scores for the red wines,
the variance change in the second group
is much more stable than the first group.
Wait, I thought the meeting started on the hour.
Why is everyone here so early?
I'm so sorry.
There's no seat for you,
Director Sang.
Come sit here.
Zhao Yue.
You stay seated.
Sit down.
I can just stand for the meeting.
My apologies.
As for the R&D Department,
we recently adjusted our work direction.
Your innovation team
won't be of much use, I'm afraid.
Then again,
you've been working for so many days
and haven't produced any results.
Since your team has nothing to do,
starting tomorrow,
you can take your team members
to the vineyard and prune the vines.
What a load of rambling nonsense.
Aren't you just targeting me?
Why drag others into this?
Since you care so much about your team,
you can go by yourself.
Fine,
Director Lin.
Hey, mister.
You can't prune the grapevines like this.
You need to leave some space.
Otherwise, they'll dry out.
Uncle An?
Why are you here?
I was banished here to do hard labor.
But as for you, Uncle An,
this doesn't seem like the pampered CEO An
would do.
I'm not CEO An anymore.
I'm just a fruit farmer now.
Then I wouldn't dare trouble you.
If you end up ruining my grapes,
I'll be the one taking the blame.
Alright, alright.
Then,
you teach me.
I'll only teach you once.
Look.
The force you used just now was right,
but your positioning was a bit off.
Here is the new bud.
You need to keep some distance from it.
Otherwise, it'll dry out.
Pruning grapevines
is a very important job for a winemaker.
Watch closely.
The pruning cut on the branch
must be a certain distance from the bud.
And the cut itself
should be as small as possible.
Because if it's too close,
the bud will be drained of moisture.
It'll die of thirst.
If the angled cut is too large,
it'll be drained of nutrients.
It'll starve.
Got it?
It has to be here.
Right at this spot.
At a 45-degree angle.
Fast,
precise,
and decisive.
Now that's perfect.
Why are you looking at me?
I just think
you out here in the orchard
are so different from back at the Cheng family.
If given a choice,
who would want to scheme every day?
If you're willing,
you can stay here forever.
Valley Breeze Group, get the hell out!
Come out! Get out here!
They're causing trouble!
Pay us back!
Give us an explanation!
Come out! Come out!
Get out here!
Come out!
Valley Breeze Group, pay us back!
Get out here right now!
Get the hell out here!
Pay us back! Brothers!
This woman...
is from Valley Breeze Group!
She's also from the Cheng family!
Please quiet down, everyone.
Tell me what's wrong.
I'll fix it for you, okay?
What else is there to say?
We work from dawn to dusk all year round
just for those few acres of vineyards.
They tore up the contract just like that!
Aren't they pushing us to a dead end?
Pay us back! - Yeah!
Pay us back!
Folks!
Folks, listen to me.
Valley Breeze Group will solve this.
Please go back for now, okay?
Give it a rest!
She's just trying to stall
to fool us! - Right!
Don't listen to her nonsense!
She just looks down on us fruit farmers.
Beat her!
I'll beat you to death!
Get lost!
Why did I ever have you?!
Such a worthless burden! - Dad...
If you delay my business again,
I'll kill you sooner or later!
Beat her! Beat her! Beat her!
I'm in charge of Valley Breeze Group.
Violence won't solve anything.
Let's sit down and talk.
Don't listen to her nonsense!
I know her!
She's the one who tore up the contract!
And now she's acting all fake.
We finally caught her today,
we cant let her go!
Don't let her go!
Keep beating her!
Beat her! Beat her! Beat her!
Beat her!
Beat her to death! Hit her hard!
Dad, I was wrong!
Don't hit me!
I'll beat you to death!
Dad, don't hit me!
Don't hit me! Dad!
Beat her!
Beat her to death!
Stop it!
Stop or I'll call the cops!
Go, go, go!
Hurry, let's go!
Are you okay?
Cheng An!
Cheng An, are you okay?
Add more. Add more.
Add some more!
Stop right there!
You stay right there!